<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<movies>
    <movie>
        <country>us</country>
        <description>A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum is a musical with music and lyrics by Stephen Sondheim and book by Burt Shevelove and Larry Gelbart.</description>
        <director>/</director>
        <duration>1''18'''</duration>
        <fileName>A-Funny-Thing-Happened-Official-Trailer-1-Michael-Crawford-M.mp4</fileName>
        <genre>Action</genre>
        <isOurSelection>false</isOurSelection>
        <language>/</language>
        <mainActors>/</mainActors>
        <name>A Funny Thing Happened</name>
        <year>1956</year>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <country>ru</country>
        <description>Alexander Nevsky (Russian: Алекса́ндр Не́вский) is a 1938 historical drama film directed by Sergei Eisenstein. It depicts the attempted invasion of Novgorod in the 13th century by the Teutonic Knights of the Holy Roman Empire and their defeat by Prince Alexander, known popularly as Alexander Nevsky (1220–1263).</description>
        <director>Sergei Eisenstein, Dmitri Vasilyev</director>
        <duration>1''18'''</duration>
        <fileName>AlexanderNevsky_ru_1938.mp4</fileName>
        <genre>/</genre>
        <isOurSelection>false</isOurSelection>
        <language>Russian</language>
        <mainActors>Nikolai Cherkasov, Nikolai Okhlopkov, Andrei Abrikosov</mainActors>
        <name>AlexanderNevsky</name>
        <year>1938</year>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <country>Ru</country>
        <description>Harry Potter is a British-American film series based on the Harry Potter novels by author J. K. Rowling. The series is distributed by Warner Bros. and consists of eight fantasy films, beginning with Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone (2001) and culminating with Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows – Part 2 (2011).[2][3] A spin-off prequel series will consist of five films, starting with F...</description>
        <director>Chris Columbus, Alfonso Cuarón, Mike Newell, David Yates</director>
        <duration>2''4'''</duration>
        <fileName>BlackOrpheus_br_1959.mp4</fileName>
        <genre>Comedy</genre>
        <isOurSelection>true</isOurSelection>
        <language>English</language>
        <mainActors>Daniel Radcliffe, Rupert Grint, Emma Watson, See below</mainActors>
        <name>Harry potter</name>
        <year>1959</year>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <country>us</country>
        <description>Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid is a 1969 American Western film directed by George Roy Hill and written by William Goldman (who won the Academy Award for Best Original Screenplay for the film). Based loosely on fact, the film tells the story of Wild West outlaws Robert LeRoy Parker, known as Butch Cassidy (Paul Newman), and his partner Harry Longabaugh, the "Sundance Kid" (Robert Redford), w...</description>
        <director>George Roy Hill</director>
        <duration>2''59'''</duration>
        <fileName>ButchCassidyAndTheSundanceKid_us_1969.mp4</fileName>
        <genre>/</genre>
        <isOurSelection>false</isOurSelection>
        <language>English</language>
        <mainActors>Paul Newman, Paul Newman, Robert Redford, Robert Redford, Katharine Ross, Katharine Ross, Strother Martin, Strother Martin, Jeff Corey, Jeff Corey, Henry Jones, Henry Jones</mainActors>
        <name>ButchCassidyAndTheSundanceKid</name>
        <year>1969</year>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <country>us</country>
        <description>Citizen Kane is a 1941 American mystery drama film by Orson Welles, its producer, co-screenwriter, director and star. The picture was Welles's first feature film. Nominated for Academy Awards in nine categories, it won an Academy Award for Best Writing (Original Screenplay) by Herman J. Mankiewicz and Welles. Considered by many critics, filmmakers, and fans to be the greatest film of all time, ...</description>
        <director>Orson Welles</director>
        <duration>3''44'''</duration>
        <fileName>CitizenKane_us_1941.mp4</fileName>
        <genre>/</genre>
        <isOurSelection>false</isOurSelection>
        <language>English</language>
        <mainActors>Orson Welles, Joseph Cotten, Joseph Cotten, Dorothy Comingore, Dorothy Comingore, Everett Sloane, Everett Sloane, Ray Collins, Ray Collins, George Coulouris, George Coulouris, Agnes Moorehead, Agnes Moorehead, Paul Stewart, Paul Stewart, Ruth Warrick, Ruth Warrick, Erskine Sanford, Erskine Sanford, William Alland, William Alland</mainActors>
        <name>CitizenKane</name>
        <year>1941</year>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <country>us</country>
        <description>/</description>
        <director>/</director>
        <duration>2''37'''</duration>
        <fileName>GoneWithTheWind_us_1939.mp4</fileName>
        <genre>/</genre>
        <isOurSelection>false</isOurSelection>
        <language>/</language>
        <mainActors>/</mainActors>
        <name>GoneWithTheWind</name>
        <year>1939</year>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <country>jp</country>
        <description>/</description>
        <director>/</director>
        <duration>1''13'''</duration>
        <fileName>Kagemusha_jp_1980.mp4</fileName>
        <genre>/</genre>
        <isOurSelection>false</isOurSelection>
        <language>/</language>
        <mainActors>/</mainActors>
        <name>Kagemusha</name>
        <year>1980</year>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <country>cn</country>
        <description>/</description>
        <director>/</director>
        <duration>2''8'''</duration>
        <fileName>liustiong_cn_2018.mp4</fileName>
        <genre>/</genre>
        <isOurSelection>false</isOurSelection>
        <language>/</language>
        <mainActors>/</mainActors>
        <name>liustiong</name>
        <year>2018</year>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <country>cn</country>
        <description>/</description>
        <director>/</director>
        <duration>2''8'''</duration>
        <fileName>LostInThailand_cn_2012.mp4</fileName>
        <genre>/</genre>
        <isOurSelection>false</isOurSelection>
        <language>/</language>
        <mainActors>/</mainActors>
        <name>LostInThailand</name>
        <year>2012</year>
    </movie>
</movies>
